Either the thrashing or the census takers, damn it
o la culerada o las censistas [__] con
all, I was 8 years old, I remember they
todo yo tenía 8 años recuerdo que me
treated me like dirt, the cars, and I didn't know what was happening,
trataron a pitt al coches y no sabía qué
and I went up to my house because at that
pasaba y subí a mi casa porque en esa
time, at eight years old, you're out on the street
época con ocho años estás en la calle
like now, in the wild streets, and I went up
como ahora en la calle salvajada y subí
to my house and what happens here are the
a mi casa y lo que pasa aquí están los
Cespa cars, we've won the league,
coches de cespa hemos ganado la liga de
playing
jugar
at 18 years old, we haven't won any
a los 18 años hayamos ganado ninguna
league, no league from the year 85, 42 years,
liga ninguna liga del año 85 42 años
we've won 17, we've had
hemos ganado 17 hemos tenido épocas
good times, we've had not so good times,
buenas hemos tenido épocas no tan buenas
mostly from the time Johan
la mayoría a partir de que llegara johan
Cruyff arrived,
cruyff
very good,
muy buenas
these eight days in 11 years, I
al llegar estos ocho días en 11 años lo
have to value it, I have to celebrate it,
tengo que valorar lo tengo que celebrar
I'm going to Canaletas, what a daddy with
me voy a canaletas que que dady con
vomit, Palacios,
vómitos palacios
very happy, happy for so
muy feliz feliz
much
por tanto